hello lovely people how are you guys
doing in today's video i'm gonna be
doing a full face
full glam full intensity full
transformative
okay i need to stop makeup look whenever
i'm about to do a very glam makeup look
i don't know why but i feel so happy
like right now i'm in a great mood i
mean i'm always in a great mood when i'm
about to do my makeup i don't know what
it is i enjoy the process then i'm going
to show you how i'm going to glam this
face
up so yeah without losing any time let's
just jump right into it i'm using my
hands so much when i'm talking it makes
me angry sometimes
especially when i'm editing while i'm
editing my videos i'm like stop
moving your hands see i'm doing it while
i'm talking about it
yes my nail is still missing it's been a
few days if you've watched my previous
video that will make sense
this is who i am now this is mood i'll
start off by priming my face
i'm using the milk makeup hydra grip
primer
[Music]
why is my skin getting so red it's like
really sensitive that's why
it looks like i have a sunburn what is
going on here
i always like putting my brow hairs in
place when i'm applying this primer
because it's so sticky
kind of puts them in place so you can
glue them on
your forehead i know it looks crazy now
that i have this all over my face i can
move on to the foundation
and today i'm not gonna use any
foundation what
see my skin is back to normal now i'm
not gonna use foundation because
whenever i wanna get that full coverage
flawless skin where everything is
covered i'm using this too
they never disappoint no that's a lie no
no they disappoint
because i can't find my perfect shade um
so i need to mix
two of them but this is the born this
way foundation sorry boring this way
concealer
by too faced and i'm gonna mix the
shades cloud and nude so
how we're gonna do this let me tell you
gonna need some lip balm first
i'm taking some of those shades on the
back of my hand
like this boom and i'm just gonna mix
them
and then i'm gonna start applying this
on my face
and i always like to leave something on
the back of my hand so that after i
blend it out if i need
some more coverage in certain areas i
can just dip my sponge and
get some more
okay guys next up i'm gonna move on to
the brows oh
it looks so weird to me when i have just
a full coverage foundation on or in my
case concealer and nothing else on
everything looks so flat you know but
we're about to change that we're just
prepping the canvas now
for the for the fun stuff i haven't
plucked my eyebrows
properly in months i'm just plucking out
those
random little hairs that are growing out
around them
but i haven't done a proper plucking
shape pink but i haven't done a proper
plucking session in a while now and i
love how they look because honestly
after
every proper packing session my brows
look completely different
and usually that proper plucking session
feels kind of fun seeing it
proper plucking session is followed by
regret
like a lot of it so now to fill in my
brows i'm gonna use the browsings pro
palette by benefit
whoa who stopped that palette what is
this
how that even happened i'm so sorry wow
that is brutal it's
deep
okay unexplainable stuff are happening
in this house
is my house hunted by ghosts angry at
brow palettes
they were probably trying to do their
brows but they weren't coming out the
way that they wanted so they got angry
and stuffed that palette
so i'll use this powder this color to
fill in my brows but once i have it on
my brush i'm gonna dip it in the wax
that's how it got dirty okay usually it
doesn't look like that it kind of looks
gross but trust me it works i'll start
off by lining the bottom part
of my brow here not trying to be very
precise
although i'm going for pretty
defined brows i'm not i won't spend too
much time filling them in you know
because that's not fun like filling your
brows i don't know about you guys but
for me
it's not the most fun part so i want to
quickly
move away from my brows fill them in and
forget about them
so that i can move on to the eyeshadows
yay
and now i'm gonna take the lightest
shade from this palette
and i will add that in the front part of
my brow
because i don't want this front part to
be very very dark my brows look a lot
more natural if i'm using
a lighter shade in the front here
by dipping that brush in your wax when
you have the brow powder on
it will make it a lot easier to create
more crisp
sharp lines just like something like a
pomade a homemade pomade
kinda diy pomade going back to the
boring this way foundation nope
concealer by too faced this is the shade
cloud and what i'm gonna do with this
is i will clean the bottom part of my
brow i'm going with that
light shade of concealer there because
it will create the illusion of more
lifted brows and as always i'm bringing
some of that concealer
on my crease i'm not dragging it all the
way down to my eyelids
just you know in my crease and right
here
i'll add a little bit of eyeshadow
primer on my eyelids
i'm blending it out
[Music]
and i'm setting all the products that i
have on my eyelids the concealer and the
eyeshadow primer
with some powder a very thin layer of
powder
over everything okay now we're moving on
to the fun part the eyeshadows
i have these two eyeshadow palettes by
nabla these are their cutie palettes
and they have different editions but
today i'm gonna use platinum
and metropolitan but yeah they have
different traditions from this palette
all of them and i mean that all of them
are so so pretty
the quality of the eyeshadows is great
and they've included so
many shimmery eyeshadows in these
palettes most of the shades
are shimmery they also have some matte
ones which is nice
so i'm gonna start off with this shade
right here it's just a very nice brown
color
nothing really unique
i'll start off by placing that color in
my crease
and i have to be careful because this
eyeshadow is very pigmented and
if i apply too much i'll have a hard
time blending it out so i'm gonna start
off by adding a small amount of time
circular motions to blend it out and
once everything is all nice and blended
i'll take some more i'm taking that
eyeshadow on the
edge of that brush you can't really tell
oh i'm not dipping my brush
like this straight into the eye shadow
i'm just taking some of it
on the edge of that brush see most of
the product is
on this edge here and then it's super
easy you guys
if you use this trick with your blending
brushes your brush will do all the
blending for you
so you place the edge with that
eyeshadow directly
in your crease so i'm sticking that edge
of that eyeshadow brush in my crease
and then i'm going left and right left
and right
circular motions and
boom everything looks really nice now
switching to the other nabla palette and
i will take this
deeper brown shade
really packing that color in the outer
third of my eye
okay something like this look how
pigmented that eyeshadow is it's crazy
switching to the sigma what is this e36
and i'll go ahead and diffuse just the
edges
this is a very tiny very precise brush
for blending i want to make sure that
between my eyelid and my crease
there is no harsh line here
[Music]
you guys know that if i'm using shimmers
i'm also using glitter glue
just to boost them a little bit i'm
going to use this glitter here it's by
too faced and i'll add it on that area
of my eyelid where i have no
eyeshadow on
quickly i'm going to take some of this
shade add it in the center
then i'm going to grab some of this one
add it in the inner corner
[Music]
i will also add a winged eyeliner to
this look
[Music]
i love this transition that we have from
the
pinkish kind of rosy shades to the more
bronzy ones
i almost poked my eye but that's okay
yeah it's very very beautiful
whoa look at it it's stunning oh
oh i love it now it's time for the
lashes we need to take care of them i'm
gonna give them a quick little curl
some mascara
oh i can't stop looking at that look
it's so pretty
no no oh just tell me why
why what i did to deserve that if this
happens to you if you get mascara on
your skin
let it dry it will be so much easier to
remove it because if i try to remove it
now it can start smudging
and creating even more mess for me i
don't want to make my life more
difficult for my fauces today
i'm going to wear a pair of by velour
lashes
i want to show you how curled these
lashes are
check them out look at that curl they're
pointing
up to the sky and they're also very very
fluffy they're so
3d i love lashes like this so i'll go
ahead and
glue them on okay time to get rid of
this
gone look how curled my lashes are
oh my god they're touching my my skin my
eyelid my crease
i don't know why they make me excited
and they're also a little bit more
heavy so i can definitely feel them on
my eyes feel like i have super long
lashes that's actually a nice feeling
you know
i kind of like that because my lashes
are short even if i coat them with
mascara they're not
that impressive so i like the feeling of
having
longer fluffier lashes if you're a
beginner with polishes
this is not a pair that you want to
start off with whoa they're intense i
like them
i'm really impressed by the curl
anyways moving on now i'm going to add
some concealer just to conceal
my under eye area i want to use this
concealer here i haven't used it in a
really long time
and this is the maybelline instant
anti-age eraser concealer
in the shade 03 fair it had a little
application
application applicator but i got rid of
it because it gets really dirty and
gross
after a few uses so i'm gonna add this
just in this little area here
i don't really have like very dark
circles under my eyes but i have some
darkness in this
inner corner here that i would like to
get rid of
this part is always very scary i've done
my makeup million times but when i get
to this part i'm always like if i mess
this up
i'll need to wipe it all off and start
over again so i'm gonna take on a very
small brush
this is the morphe m516
i'm gonna take some of that brown shade
which i used in the crease
and i will add that
under my lower lashes i'm always
very scared that i might overdo this oh
my concealer is creasing here
and i'm stopping right in the center
here i'm gonna take my blending brush
and blend it out
[Music]
and now i'm gonna take some of that
brown shade which i used
[Music]
i dropped my brush which i used in the
outer corner of my
eye this one here and i'm gonna add it
in the very
outer corner of my lower lash line
and i'm kind of connecting it with the
eyeliner here
once i blend it out it will start
looking so much better
[Music]
i want to make sure that everything
looks connected
before setting my concealer under the
eyes i always press it with my finger
like this and this is getting rid of any
creases
and it also takes away the excess
product
i'm gonna add some powder under my eyes
to set that concealer in place
a very thin layer of powder all right
whoa
what an eye look i love it it's very
intense you guys it's
something that i wouldn't usually wear
on my everyday bases
i would need a very super extra special
occasion to wear i look like that i'm
gonna take some of this bronzer i tried
this one out in my previous video
and wow it's a really nice bronzer i'm
gonna add some of it on the top of my
forehead here
blending it into my hairline this will
kind of contour my forehead
and add some color i may also add some
on my cheeks
like this
and also some blush i'm using this one
here by colourpop it's really nice pinky
blush
and whoa i think i applied a little bit
too much but
this will bring some color back on my
face because those concealers
are full coverage concealers so they
covered
basically everything and you know i want
to bring back
some color gonna make everything look a
little bit more fresh a little bit more
alive and i also think that blush gives
you that
youthful look we're definitely going for
something more elegant today but that
doesn't mean that we don't want to look
fresh
i love blush so much next up i will line
my lips with some lip pencil this one is
by kevin aquan and the shade is called
divine i'm also filling in my lips with
it
and some lip gloss on top
[Music]
now i'm gonna take this hourglass
champagne flush highlighter and i
wouldn't use that but i don't want to
overdo it
i don't want to go with a crazy super
bright highlighter day
today i want to add you know a little
bit of a glow but nothing really too
crazy
because the eyes are already very
dramatic and the lips as well
so i'm gonna take some of that
highlighter on my sponge i'm gonna add
it on my face
that's probably enough
lastly i had somewhere here my favorite
pencil for my waterline yep it's right
here i've been using this one probably
what happened computer anyways i've been
using this for
over a year and i still have
can you just please stop and i'm always
using that in my waterline because it
adds very nice brightness to the look
especially with more dark looks like
this one makes everything a little bit
more
you know bright it also gives me that
more like
dolly kind of eyes more cartoonish
and by the way i left this one on my
desk or you know around the house
so many times without its cup and i'm
always like so disappointed when i find
it just sitting somewhere like this
without its cup but it's still
so nice and creamy it still applies like
the first time i used it it's really
nice
oh i just found out that you're supposed
to use this for only six months after
opening it and i've been using it
probably three times more than that
yeah i can easily say that it's it's
been over an year and a half
oh no i need to get a new one but i
still have so much of it left
hold on oh that's a lot of pencil that's
a lot of product okay okay i'm
definitely getting a new one after i did
this
why did i do that was this little guy
there the whole time
interesting there we go
oh you're one of those huh you don't
give up easily huh
i'm gonna show you now that's better
guys let me know if you would wear
a look like that and if you would wear i
love it
so so much that inner corner glow
is so beautiful let's not talk about my
love about shimmers at least in one of
my videos okay
you guys have heard me talk about it so
many times so let's just
skip it for once i would only wear a
look like that
for a very special occasion i already
said that it's a very dramatic look
don't think that i'm going out like this
like every day i don't looks like that
require time they require patience but
they're very fun to create and they're
very fun to watch somebody create it
looks
magical you guys i can't believe how
beautiful it looks
this definitely goes in the folder of my
favorite looks for 2020. if you guys
decide to recreate any of my looks make
sure that you tag me on instagram
because i love love love seeing your
recreations talking about instagram if
you guys don't follow me on there
you can go ahead and do it now i post
some photos of the looks that i'm
creating here on youtube i'm also
posting some other photos
i mean instagram is for posting photos
duh i don't know where i was going with
that i was just trying to self-promote
myself okay
thank you if you guys enjoyed watching
this video please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up subscribe to my
channel if you're not already
because that helps me a lot thank you so
so so so much for watching and hopefully
i'll see you in my next one bye
you